rocksbox.com 2014-03-25

# RocksBox

##### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or analytics.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

##### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience   
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To process transactions

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.  
To send periodic emails

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

##### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

##### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service.

##### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

##### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

##### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the ‘My Account’ page.

##### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

##### Analytics

Information Collected From All Visitors Visitors to this website who have javascript enabled are tracked using Google Analytics. Google Analytics collects the following types of information from users: Type of user agent (web browser) used, software manufacture and version number. Type of operating system Screen colors (color processing ability of the users screen) Javascript support Flash version Screen resolution Network location and IP address Can include country, city, state, region, county, or any other geographic data. Hostname Bandwidth (internet connection speed) Time of visit Pages visited Time spent on each page of the website Referring site statistics The website (URI) the user came through in order to arrive at this website (example: clicking on a hyperlink from Yahoo.com that took the user to this website) Search engine query used (example: typing in a phrase into a search engine like Google, and clicking on a link from that search engine) This data is primarily used to optimize our website for our visitors, however we will use this data for marketing purposes. An example of how this data could be used for marketing purposes would be to tell potential advertisers how many visitors we get to the website, where our visitors come from, and how they arrive at our website.

##### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

##### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

##### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on September 30, 2013

##### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

http://www.rocksbox.com/

95 Minna Street, 4th Floor  
San Francisco, CA 94105  
members@rocksbox.com

##### Introduction

These terms and conditions govern your use of this website; by using this website, you accept these terms and conditions in full. If you disagree with these terms and conditions or any part of these terms and conditions, you must not use this website.

##### License to use website

Unless otherwise stated, RocksBox and/or its licensors own the intellectual property rights in the website and material on the website. Subject to the license below, all these intellectual property rights are reserved.

You may view, download for caching purposes only, and print pages from the website for your own personal use, subject to the restrictions set out below and elsewhere in these terms and conditions.

You must not:

  * republish material from this website (including republication on another website);
  * sell, rent or sub-license material from the website;
  * show any material from the website in public;
  * reproduce, duplicate, copy or otherwise exploit material on this website for a commercial purpose;
  * edit or otherwise modify any material on the website; or
  * redistribute material from this website except for content specifically and expressly made available for redistribution.

##### Acceptable use

You must not use this website in any way that causes, or may cause, damage to the website or impairment of the availability or accessibility of the website; or in any way which is unlawful, illegal, fraudulent or harmful, or in connection with any unlawful, illegal, fraudulent or harmful purpose or activity.

You must not use this website to copy, store, host, transmit, send, use, publish or distribute any material which consists of (or is linked to) any spyware, computer virus, Trojan horse, worm, keystroke logger, rootkit or other malicious computer software.

You must not conduct any systematic or automated data collection activities (including without limitation scraping, data mining, data extraction and data harvesting) on or in relation to this website without the express written consent of RocksBox, Inc.

You must not use this website to transmit or send unsolicited commercial communications.

You must not use this website for any purposes related to marketing without RocksBox, Inc.’s express written consent.

##### Restricted access

Access to certain areas of this website is restricted. RocksBox, Inc. reserves the right to restrict access to [other] areas of this website, or indeed this entire website, at RocksBox, Inc.’s discretion.

If RocksBox, Inc. provides you with a user ID and password to enable you to access restricted areas of this website or other content or services, you must ensure that the user ID and password are kept confidential.

RocksBox, Inc. may disable your user ID and password in RocksBox, Inc.’s sole discretion without notice or explanation.

##### User content

In these terms and conditions, “your user content” means material (including without limitation text, images, audio material, video material and audio-visual material) that you submit to this website, for whatever purpose.

You grant to RocksBox, Inc. a worldwide, irrevocable, non-exclusive, royalty-free license to use, reproduce, adapt, publish, translate and distribute your user content in any existing or future media. You also grant to RocksBox, Inc. the right to sub-license these rights, and the right to bring an action for infringement of these rights.

Your user content must not be illegal or unlawful, must not infringe any third party’s legal rights, and must not be capable of giving rise to legal action whether against you or RocksBox, Inc. or a third party (in each case under any applicable law).

You must not submit any user content to the website that is or has ever been the subject of any threatened or actual legal proceedings or other similar complaint.

RocksBox, Inc. reserves the right to edit or remove any material submitted to this website, or stored on RocksBox, Inc.’s servers, or hosted or published upon this website.

##### No warranties

This website is provided “as is” without any representations or warranties, express or implied. RocksBox, Inc. makes no representations or warranties in relation to this website or the information and materials provided on this website.

Without prejudice to the generality of the foregoing paragraph, RocksBox, Inc. does not warrant that:

  * this website will be constantly available, or available at all; or
  * the information on this website is complete, true, accurate or non-misleading.

Nothing on this website constitutes, or is meant to constitute, advice of any kind. If you require advice in relation to matter you should consult an appropriate professional.

##### Limitations of liability

RocksBox, Inc. will not be liable to you (whether under the law of contact, the law of torts or otherwise) in relation to the contents of, or use of, or otherwise in connection with, this website:

  * to the extent that the website is provided free-of-charge, for any direct loss;
  * for any indirect, special or consequential loss; or
  * for any business losses, loss of revenue, income, profits or anticipated savings, loss of contracts or business relationships, loss of reputation or goodwill, or loss or corruption of information or data.

These limitations of liability apply even if RocksBox, Inc. has been expressly advised of the potential loss.

##### Exceptions

Nothing in this website disclaimer will exclude or limit any warranty implied by law that it would be unlawful to exclude or limit; and nothing in this website disclaimer will exclude or limit RocksBox, Inc.’s liability in respect of any:

  * death or personal injury caused by RocksBox, Inc.’s negligence;
  * fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation on the part of RocksBox, Inc.; or
  * matter which it would be illegal or unlawful for RocksBox, Inc. to exclude or limit, or to attempt or purport to exclude or limit, its liability.

##### Reasonableness

By using this website, you agree that the exclusions and limitations of liability set out in this website disclaimer are reasonable.

If you do not think they are reasonable, you must not use this website.

##### Other parties

You accept that, as a limited liability entity, RocksBox, Inc. has an interest in limiting the personal liability of its officers and employees. You agree that you will not bring any claim personally against RocksBox, Inc.’s officers or employees in respect of any losses you suffer in connection with the website.

You agree that the limitations of warranties and liability set out in this website disclaimer will protect RocksBox, Inc.’s officers, employees, agents, subsidiaries, successors, assigns and sub-contractors as well as RocksBox, Inc.

##### Unenforceable provisions

If any provision of this website disclaimer is, or is found to be, unenforceable under applicable law, that will not affect the enforceability of the other provisions of this website disclaimer.

##### Indemnity

You hereby indemnify RocksBox, Inc. and undertake to keep RocksBox, Inc. indemnified against any losses, damages, costs, liabilities and expenses (including without limitation legal expenses and any amounts paid by RocksBox, Inc. to a third party in settlement of a claim or dispute on the advice of RocksBox, Inc.’s legal advisers) incurred or suffered by RocksBox, Inc. arising out of any breach by you of any provision of these terms and conditions, or arising out of any claim that you have breached any provision of these terms and conditions.

##### Breaches of these terms and conditions

Without prejudice to RocksBox, Inc.’s other rights under these terms and conditions, if you breach these terms and conditions in any way, RocksBox, Inc. may take such action as RocksBox, Inc. deems appropriate to deal with the breach, including suspending your access to the website, prohibiting you from accessing the website, blocking computers using your IP address from accessing the website, contacting your internet service provider to request that they block your access to the website and/or bringing court proceedings against you.

##### Variation

RocksBox, Inc. may revise these terms and conditions from time-to-time. Revised terms and conditions will apply to the use of this website from the date of the publication of the revised terms and conditions on this website. Please check this page regularly to ensure you are familiar with the current version.

##### Assignment

RocksBox, Inc. may transfer, sub-contract or otherwise deal with RocksBox, Inc.’s rights and/or obligations under these terms and conditions without notifying you or obtaining your consent.

You may not transfer, sub-contract or otherwise deal with your rights and/or obligations under these terms and conditions.

##### Severability

If a provision of these terms and conditions is determined by any court or other competent authority to be unlawful and/or unenforceable, the other provisions will continue in effect. If any unlawful and/or unenforceable provision would be lawful or enforceable if part of it were deleted, that part will be deemed to be deleted, and the rest of the provision will continue in effect.

##### Entire agreement

These terms and conditions, together with the Privacy Policy, constitute the entire agreement between you and RocksBox, Inc. in relation to your use of this website, and supersede all previous agreements in respect of your use of this website.

##### Law and jurisdiction

These terms and conditions will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Delaware and the United States of America, and any disputes relating to these terms and conditions will be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of Delaware.

##### RocksBox, Inc.’s details

RocksBox, Inc. is registered in Delaware.

RocksBox, Inc.’s address is 95 Minna Street, 4th Floor, San Francisco, CA 94105

You can contact RocksBox, Inc. by email to members@rocksbox.com.
